export const lvl3 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What large park is located in the center of Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Botanic Gardens', 'B) Central Park', 'C) Royal Park'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Botanic Gardens',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What river flows through Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Murray', 'B) Brisbane River', 'C) Darling'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane River',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What nature reserve is located near Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      "A) D'Aguilar National Park",
      'B) Blue Mountains National Park',
      'C) Great Sandy National Park',
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A) D'Aguilar National Park",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What type of animal can be seen at the Lone Pine Koala Sanctuary?`,
    answers: ['A) Kangaroo', 'B) Koala', 'C) Emu'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Koala',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What popular beach is located near Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Surfers Paradise', 'B) Moreton Island', 'C) Bondi Beach'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Moreton Island',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What park on the Brisbane River is perfect for picnics?`,
    answers: ['A) Roma Street Parkland', 'B) Hyde Park', 'C) Kings Park'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Roma Street Parkland',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What famous bridge connects both banks of the Brisbane River?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Sydney Harbour Bridge',
      'B) Story Bridge',
      'C) Golden Gate Bridge',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Story Bridge',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What animal species is protected in Queensland's wildlife?`,
    answers: ['A) Mammals', 'B) Cockroaches', 'C) Kangaroos'],
    correctAnswer: 'C) Kangaroos',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What national park is located near Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Lamington National Park',
      'B) Kakadu National Park',
      'C) Uluru-Kata Tjuta National Park',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Lamington National Park',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What type of ecosystem predominates in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Tropical rainforest', 'B) Desert', 'C) Subtropical forest'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Tropical rainforest',
  },
];
